# William Hall

(803)414-9580 whhall@email.sc.edu whhall.github.io

#### **Professional Summary**

Junior Majoring in Information Science at the University of South Carolina and successful graduate of Midlands Technical College with an Associates in Computer Technology and recipient of the TechHire Front End Programming Scholarship. Six years of customer service and two years of web development experience. Passionate about learning, solving problems, and creating positive customer experiences. I love data! Check out my personal

#### **Technical Skills**

Programming: Java, Python, R, Javascript, AJAX, HTML, CSS, SQL

Software: Microsoft Office 365, Adobe Creative Suite, Visual Studio, Git, Github

Operating Systems: Windows 7/8.1/10, Ubuntu Linux, Android, IOS

#### Education

#### University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC

Bachelor of Science in Information Science Expected Graduation May 2021

#### Midlands Technical College, Columbia, SC

Associate of Applied Science in Computer Technology	Aug. 2017 – May 2019
TechHire Front End Programming Scholarship	May 2019 – Aug. 2019

#### Work Experience

## Department of Education, Columbia, SC **Web Development Intern**

August 2019 – January 2020

- Developing UI/UX standards for all department web applications.
- Designing responsive web templates using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap 4.
- Analyzing requirements and implementing solutions based on departmental needs.
- Formatting and editing media and infographics for web usage using Adobe Creative Suite.
- Communicating with team members in daily SCRUM sessions, Outlook, and Teams.

### 116 Wine and Espresso, Columbia, SC Bartender/Manager

June 2018 – April 2019

- Created a unique experience for all guests with an unmatched level of customer service.
- Managed all monetary transactions throughout establishment.
- Coordinated teams of five or more dining room and kitchen staff.
- Educated in mixology and wine with emphasis on European varietals.

# Thirsty Fellow, Columbia, SC

November 2013 – June 2018

#### Waiter

- Excelled at developing relationships with customers and creating repeat business.
- Upheld high level of organization while multitasking in a fast-paced environment.
- Voted best waiter in Columbia by Free Times 2014.
- Increased revenue using soft sales and upselling techniques.